plumdistrict.com 2013-06-06

# Deals and Coupons for Moms | Fun Family & Kid Activities, Restaurants, Health & Beauty, Clothing and more | PlumDistrict.com

Effective April 14, 2011

Plum District, Inc. (“Plum District”, “our”, “us” or “we”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of http://www.plumdistrict.com/ (this “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Plum District Terms of Service, accessible at http://www.plumdistrict.com/p/terms.

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

### Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content, to administer your use of the Site (together, the “Service”) and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.

#### Personally Identifiable Information.

  * When you (i) register with us through the Site to become a Plum District Member, (ii) elect to receive email deal alerts or (iii) choose to make a purchase of a Voucher through the Site, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, free-form biography, credit card or other billing information, email address and postal address. We use your Personal Information to provide the Service and administer your inquiries. 
  * You can register to join Plum District via the Site or by logging into your account with certain third party services providing authentication services (“Third Party Services”) (including, but not limited to, Facebook) via our Site. If you decide to create your Account by logging into an Third Party Service via the Site, we will extract the Personal Information you have provided to the Third Party Service (such as your “real” name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the Third Party Service) from the account you have with such Third Party Service and use that information to create your Account; the information we extract may depend on the privacy settings you have with the Third Party Service. For example, our Service allows users to create an account and login to the Service using their Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. If you are not currently registered as a Member and you click on “Facebook Connect”, you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials. By providing your credentials via Facebook Connect, you will register with Plum District and you will allow Plum District to access the information that, through your settings on Facebook, you have elected to share with third parties. By using Facebook Connect, you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use regarding your use of the Service via Facebook. We also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your account (e.g., without limitation, gender, zip code (on its own), transaction history and individual preferences) (“Non-Identifying Information”). 
  * We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries. 
  * Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Plum District Users (defined below) to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how our Site and Service are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions. 
  * We also use your Personal Information to contact you with Plum District newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or select “My Subscriptions” on the Site. (See “Changing or Deleting Information” below.) 

#### Surveys and Polls.

From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys and polls (each a “Survey”) via our Service. If you participate in a Survey, some of the information you provide may be visible to others using the Site. We may also request certain Personal Information from you if you participate in a Survey. We use the Personal Information you provide to us in these instances to administer your participation in the Survey. Participation in a Survey is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. You may opt out of participating by contacting us.

#### Log Data

When you visit the Site, whether as a Plum District member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “Plum District User”), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Site’s technical administration, to increase our Site’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors’ needs. For example, some of this information is collected so that when you visit the Site again, it will recognize you and serve advertisements and other information appropriate to your interests. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Site meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information.

### Cookies and Other Technologies

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by Plum District Users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Service and then close your browser. We may also use “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “clear GIFs” or similar means (individually or collectively “Pixel Tags”) in connection with our Site to collect usage data. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel that is ordinarily not visible to users and may be associated with cookies on a user’s hard drive. Pixel Tags help us to determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and allow us to deliver targeted advertising to you regarding our Services when you visit the websites of our advertising partners. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. Plum District does not have access to or control of any cookies that its advertisers may store in your browser and this Privacy Policy does not apply to the use of cookies by advertisers. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the web sites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all the functionality of the Service.

### Sending a Gift via Plum District

As part of the Service, Members may purchase Vouchers as gifts for third parties. Where a Member has selected the option of giving a Voucher as a gift, Plum District will collect the name and email address of the intended recipient, and the message such Member creates in the corresponding template will be sent from Plum District to the email addresses provided on such Member’s behalf. The name and email address of the gift recipient will be used only for the purpose of sending the email communication containing the Voucher to such gift recipient.

### Emailing Via a Plum District Account

If a Member chooses to refer a friend to the Service, Plum District will collect such friend’s email address. Where a Member selects the option of adding one or more email addresses our online friend referral form, the message created in the corresponding form will be sent from Plum District to those email addresses on such Member’s behalf. These email addresses will be used only for the purpose of sending the email communication to the addressees.

### Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to Plum District. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, login information, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

#### Plum District Users.

If you are a Plum District district consultant or if you choose to comment or post any other information on the Site, other Plum District Users will see your first name, photo, city and state, free-form biography and the other information you choose to submit to the Service. Providing this information is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with Plum District Users. We recommend that you guard sensitive information.

#### Third Party Services.

We may share the information in your Account (including your Personal Information) with the Third Party Services that you have linked to your Account. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only for this purpose (unless the Third Party Service has received your Personal Information independently of the Service) and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### Facebook Connect.

We allow Members to automatically post recent activity back to Facebook via Facebook Connect. A Member may disable the connection between the Service and Facebook Connect at any time by accessing his or her Facebook account and selecting the option to disable Facebook Connect.

#### Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information.

We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

#### Service Providers.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, accounting, maintenance services, payment processing, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### Merchants.

We will share your name, state, email address and shipping address (if applicable) with the Merchants from whom you purchase Vouchers through the Service, together with a unique Voucher number that associates the Voucher with you. For example, when you make a purchase of a Voucher through Plum District, we will provide your name, state, email address and shipping address (if applicable) to the applicable Merchant who issued and sold the Voucher for the successful fulfillment of your purchase. Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. Plum District cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Plum District or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

#### Business Transfers.

Plum District may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

### Changing or Deleting Your Information

All Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their Accounts by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your Account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your Account from our system, please contact us at help@plumdistrict.com with a request that we delete your Personal Information from our database. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

### Security

Limited to Specific Security Measures for Sensitive Info e.g. We do not take measures to protect non-sensitive PII  – “Plum District is very concerned with safeguarding your information. The security of your personal information is important to us.  But remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.  When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  In some cases, we also encrypt sensitive information where it is stored on our systems.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

### International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Plum District transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### Links to Other Sites and Services

Our Site contains links to other websites, online services or applications (each a “Third Party Service”), e.g.: Your Account may be linked to an SNS and links to Merchants’ websites may be available on the Site. If you click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website or online service. The fact that we link to a Third Party Service is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over Third Party Services. Such Third Party Services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites and online services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other Third Party Services you visit.

### Our Policy Toward Children

This Site is not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at privacy@plumdistrict.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@plumdistrict.com or at: 77 Stillman Street, San Francisco, California 94107.
